leaf3 =[
{"question":"亂動","Answer":"luàndòng"},
{"question":"矮小","Answer":"ǎixiǎo"},
{"question":"戴","Answer":"dài"},
{"question":"頂","Answer":"dǐng"},
{"question":"貝雷帽","Answer":"bèiléimào"},
{"question":"蓬鬆","Answer":"péng sōng"},
{"question":"鬍子","Answer":"hú zi"},
{"question":"叼","Answer":"diāo"},
{"question":"根","Answer":"gēn"},
{"question":"煙斗","Answer":"yāndǒu"},
{"question":"開銷","Answer":"kāixiāo"},
{"question":"貝阿蒙","Answer":"bèi āméng"},
{"question":"熱情","Answer":"rèqíng"},
{"question":"爬山虎","Answer":"páshānhǔ"},
{"question":"微醺","Answer":"wēixūn"},
{"question":"礦工","Answer":"kuànggōng"},
{"question":"模特兒","Answer":"mótè r"},
{"question":"討厭","Answer":"tǎoyàn"},
{"question":"模特兒","Answer":"mótè r"},
{"question":"瓊絲","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"概","Answer":"gài"},
{"question":"舒服","Answer":"shūfu"},
{"question":"撐","Answer":"chēng"},
{"question":"憐惜","Answer":"liánxī"},
{"question":"沈默","Answer":"chénmò"},
{"question":"片刻","Answer":"piànkè"},
{"question":"貝阿蒙","Answer":"bèi āméng"},
{"question":"逗","Answer":"dòu"},
{"question":"眼色","Answer":"yǎnsè"},
{"question":"瓊絲","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"沈沈","Answer":"shěnshěn"},
{"question":"窗簾","Answer":"chuānglián"},
{"question":"手勢","Answer":"shǒushì"},
{"question":"隔壁","Answer":"gébì"},
{"question":"窗","Answer":"chuāng"},
{"question":"棵","Answer":"kē"},
{"question":"爬山虎","Answer":"páshānhǔ"},
{"question":"剩","Answer":"shèng"},
{"question":"片","Answer":"piàn"},
{"question":"彼此","Answer":"bǐcǐ"},
{"question":"心照不宣","Answer":"xīnzhàobùxuān"},
{"question":"窗","Answer":"chuāng"},
{"question":"持續","Answer":"chíxù"},
{"question":"摻雜","Answer":"chānzá"},
{"question":"風雪","Answer":"fēngxuě"},
{"question":"破舊","Answer":"pòjiù"},
{"question":"褪","Answer":"tuì"},
{"question":"藍襯衫","Answer":"lán chènshān"},
{"question":"擺","Answer":"bǎi"},
{"question":"副","Answer":"fù"}
]